officedepot.com 2011-10-07

# Customer Service at Office Depot

Updated: June 17, 2010

It is Office Depot Inc.'s and its affiliates' and subsidiaries' (collectively "Office Depot, we or us") policy to respect and protect the privacy of our customers and users of www.officedepot.com, [www.myworkliferewards.com](http://www.myworkliferewards.com/) and all other websites and mobile text programs operated by Office Depot (hereinafter, the "Site"). Through this Privacy Statement, we want to reassure users that we will not sell, share, or rent user information to others in a manner different than in this Privacy Statement. **By accessing the Site, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, please do not use the Site. Each time you use the Site, the current version of this Privacy Statement will apply. When you use the Site you should check the date of this Privacy Statement (which appears at the top) and review any changes since the last version.**

## Placing Orders and Information Collection

Office Depot collects information from users of the Site at several different points, including, without limitation when a user: 

1\. Places an order 

2\. Registers on the Site 

3\. Requests notification of an order status 

4\. Participates in an online sweepstakes or survey 

5\. Applies for a credit card 

6\. Requests a catalog 

7\. Submits an e-mail 

8\. Subscribes to receive e-mail or mobile SMS text messages 

9\. Sends an SMS text message to Depot (33768)

In order to fulfill the requests of Site users in the above instances, the user may be requested to provide contact and/or credit card information. If we have trouble processing an order, a request, completing a delivery, or such other similar issue this contact information will be used by Office Depot or a third party working on our behalf to contact the user.

## Gathering and Sharing of Information, Links to External and Co-Branded Websites

We monitor traffic patterns on the Site for aggregate use to analyze trends and administer the Site to improve its layout, design, and provide unique offers to users. We also monitor traffic patterns to permit Site personalization and streamlining to create a positive shopping experience for our users, this is known as behavioral marketing. To perform analysis permitting such personalization and improvement, we may employ third parties with whom we share the information necessary to accomplish these objectives. These statistics include no personally identifying information. 

Where appropriate, we share aggregated statistical information with our business partners. These statistics include no personally identifying information. 

We use a credit card processing company to bill purchasers of goods and services from the Site, and depending upon the goods and services being ordered and where they are being shipped, we may also use outside suppliers and/or delivery companies to assist us in fulfilling and delivering orders. We share with them the information necessary to enable such card processing, fulfillment, delivery of goods, etc. (e.g., name, address, and as appropriate, payment information). 

Additionally, we partner with trusted third parties to provide Site users with offers or services that may be of value to our users. In these instances, we may share, sell or rent a user's name, phone number, postal address or ordering information to third parties to enable them to notify appropriate users of such offers or services. We will never provide credit card information and you will always be provided with the opportunity to unsubscribe from any such list. 

Except as stated below, we will not share, sell or rent your e-mail address or mobile phone number to third parties. But, we may do so between our affiliates and subsidiaries. We may, however, share e-mail addresses or mobile phone numbers with reputable third parties in order to help us provide better services. These third parties agree not use your information for their own marketing purposes. 

We may provide personally identifying and/or account information in special cases such as enforcement of our Terms of Use, as required by law or legal process to protect and defend the rights and safety of Office Depot, our Site, and its users. This includes exchanging information with other companies for purposes of fraud and credit risk reduction. 

Our Site also contains links to external Internet sites as well as co-branded sites, which may be operated by an external party. These sites may have privacy practices different from ours. A co-branded site is a website, usually operated by a third-party, and which displays that third-party's name along with the Office Depot name and logo. Such co-branded sites offer goods or services to our users. When you click on links that take you to such external or co-branded sites, you will be subject to its privacy policies, and we encourage you to become familiar with that party's privacy policies as these may differ from ours. Please note that this Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by Office Depot on our Site and, while we strongly support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other websites, uses of the information collected by other websites, or the content of those other websites.

## Consent

By using our Site, you agree to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Statement and the Site Terms of Use INCLUDING ALL LIMITATIONS OF DAMAGES PROVISIONS, which are an integral part of this Privacy Statement. By using our Site, you also consent to the collection and use of this information by Office Depot as disclosed in this Privacy Statement.

## Security Information

Strong precautions are taken to protect the information of the users of our Site. When users submit sensitive information via the Site, we attempt to protect that information both online and off-line. 

We take credit card information security seriously and use a variety of technical solutions to make shopping safe at our Site. Furthermore, we encrypt and protect your information utilizing the industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption software. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Firefox and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also protect user-information off-line. The information of our Site's users, including the sensitive information mentioned above, is maintained in a restricted section in our offices. Only those of our employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our account or customer service representatives) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, our employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or across mobile carriers and networks, or method of storage - electronic or otherwise - can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. IN NO EVENT SHALL OFFICE DEPOT BE LIABLE FOR SPECIAL, INDIRECT, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS, WITHOUT REGARD TO THE FORM OF ANY ACTION, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTIONS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, COPYING, OR DISPLAY OF THE CONTENTS OF THE SITE, EVEN IF OFFICE DEPOT OR AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OF OFFICE DEPOT HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. 

If you have any questions about the security at our Site, you can send an e-mail to [orders@officedepot.com](mailto:orders@officedepot.com).

## Cookies

You may have heard of the term "cookies." Cookies are routinely used by most, if not all, e- commerce merchants, including Office Depot. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive through the web browser program containing information about the user that enables us to track and personalize the Site to enhance your experience. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, we can provide you with storage of items in your shopping cart between visits. However, if a user rejects the cookie, he or she may still use our Site although we will be unable to provide such users with the personalized shopping experience we can offer using the cookie data. If you have any questions about our use of cookies, please contact us at [orders@officedepot.com](mailto:orders@officedepot.com).

## Surveys, Sweepstakes & Contests

From time-to-time we may request information from the users of the Site via surveys, sweepstakes or contests. Participation in these surveys, sweepstakes or contests is completely voluntary, and the users of the Site have a choice whether or not to participate. Information requested may include contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code, age level, etc.). We use such information to notify contest winners, to award prizes, and to analyze the Site traffic to improve the user's experience on the Site. All participation in such surveys, sweepstakes and contests are subject to the applicable rules and terms and conditions.

## Children's On-line Privacy

Office Depot recognizes the particular importance of protecting the privacy of children. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. When a user makes a purchase on the Site, the user is representing to us that he or she is an adult. If a child provides the Site with personally identifiable information, we ask that a parent or guardian call 1-800-GO-DEPOT (463-3768). We will then delete the personally identifiable information pertaining to the child from our records.

## Special Offers, Account Updates and Opting Out

Office Depot occasionally sends our customers and the users of the Site announcements and updates, which contain important information about the Site and service offerings, including those from affiliates, which we believe to be of value to our customers and users. In order to do this, we may enhance or merge the information we collect on the Site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to our customers and users. 

We may communicate with the users of the Site via e-mail, telephone, mail, fax, or SMS text message in order to provide services, content, product information, notification of offers, discounts, or in regard to customer service issues relating to an account. The users of the Site are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of receiving certain marketing communications. 

For example, our e-mail messages have an "unsubscribe" feature for users of the Site who buy from us, but do not want to be notified about special offers in the future. Users can simply "Reply" back to the e-mail message and type "unsubscribe" in the subject field. We will remove that e-mail address from our e-mail list. If a user has more than one e-mail address, he or she must include the other email addresses as well to ensure proper updating of account information. In addition, users who have an account on the Site can opt out of receiving promotional e-mail by going to: [www.officedepot.com/account/editContactDisplay.do](https://www.officedepot.com/account/editContactDisplay.do?&jtime=1317947533844&jvalidator=nDayjP9eEiq7NwUx6RlQsg%3D%3D). 

If you do not wish to have your postal mail information, phone number or ordering information shared with third-party organizations, users can opt out by: (i) telephone at 1-800-915-4624; (ii) mail at Office Depot Mail Listing, P.O. Box 5009, Boca Raton, Florida 33431-0809, or (iii) e-mail at [mailoptout@officedepot.com](mailto:mailoptout@officedepot.com). Please indicate whether you wish to continue to receive Office Depot's catalogs and other postal mailings. In addition, users who have an account on the Site can opt out of receiving postal mail by going to: [www.officedepot.com/account/editContactDisplay.do](https://www.officedepot.com/account/editContactDisplay.do?&jtime=1317947533844&jvalidator=nDayjP9eEiq7NwUx6RlQsg%3D%3D). 

If you wish to opt-out of our SMS text message service(s), reply 'STOP' to any message or text 'STOP' to Depot (33768). Users of the Site can always update the personally identifying information that they have provided to Office Depot simply by accessing and updating their account information on the Site or by e-mailing us at [orders@officedepot.com](mailto:orders@officedepot.com). 

  *
